naturalhairmag.com 2013-04-16

# Privacy Policy - Natural Hair Mag

Natural Hair Mag (Company, we, us or our) takes steps to ensure it meets privacy principles and requirements with respect to personal information under applicable privacy legislation. This Privacy Policy only applies to transactions made, and data gathered, on the Natural Hair Mag website (Site). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform users of this Site (you or your) how we collect, use, disclose and protect your personal information. This Policy applies to our online collection, use and disclosure of personal information in theUnited States.

By using this Site, you expressly and affirmatively consent to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, as described below. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy please do not provide us any information and do not use this Site.

Please review thisPrivacyStateperiodically as we may update it from time to time.

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Natural Hair Mag and its agents and representatives collect personal information in a number of circumstances in order to operate the Site.

Personal Information we collect includes:

Name, address, email address, telephone number, cell phone number and other business and/or residential contact information;  
Financial information such as credit card or bank account numbers and other financial information required to complete a transaction;  
Transactional information based on your activities on the Site (including bids, purchases and shipping information);  
Information or comments you provide to us on the Site or otherwise or that you provide to others via the Site;  
Registration information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, and other information, including IP address and standard web log information; and  
Such other information we may collect with consent or as permitted or required by law.

Please note that nowhere on the Site do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION OR DATA

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to facilitate your use of the Site and the services that we provide. You agree that we may use your personal information for the following purposes:

Identification and verification;  
Establishment and maintenance of our relationship with you;  
Process transaction #(including billing and shipping) and provide customer support to you;  
Protect you, and us, against error and fraud;  
Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use;  
Customize, measure and improve our services and the Sites content and layout;  
Marketing (i.e., tell you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences);  
Compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties  
Maintaining business records for reasonable periods, and generally managing and administering our business;  
Meeting legal, regulatory, insurance, security and processing requirements; and  
Otherwise with consent or as permitted or required by law.

See the section on  Your Consent below regarding how to decline consent to marketing purposes.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may disclose personal information to process transactions, facilitate events and other administrative purposes, respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that content or services violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.

We may also share your personal information with:

Members of our corporate family including affiliates in order to provide services and to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts;  
Venues, promoters, artists, artists representatives, fan clubs, and others that are involved in, produce and bring you events (Event Providers);  
Service providers who facilitate our operations (i.e., internet providers, credit card processors, marketing agencies, collection agencies, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards);  
other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information; (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service);  
law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity; and  
other business entities in connection with financing, securitization, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of Company or our business or assets, including for the purposes of: permitting such parties to determine whether to proceed or continue with such transaction (in the event that all or part of Company or our business or assets is sold, assigned or otherwise disposed of, personal information we have collected will be used and disclosed by such parties for substantially the same purposes as described in this Policy).

We take reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information collected, used, disclosed or otherwise processed by affiliates and third parties is protected and not used or disclosed for purposes other than as directed by us, subject to requirements in foreign jurisdictions applicable to those organizations. Note that some of these jurisdictions do not have personal information protection laws equivalent to those in theUnited States.

We may otherwise disclose personal information as necessary to meet legal, regulatory, insurance, audit, and security requirements.

We will not be responsible or otherwise liable for any use or disclosure of your contact information by a third party to whom we are allowed to disclose your contact information under this privacy Policy.

COOKIES

We from time to time use cookies on this Site. Cookies are small text files that your web browser leaves on your hard drive to recognize you as a repeat user of our Site, track your use of our Site and target advertising. This allows for personalization of certain aspects of your visit to our Site. Information gathered from cookies in this way is only used on an aggregate basis. Unless a visitor specifically provides their identity to us, e.g., by registering at our Site, providing information through an online form or sending us correspondence from the Site, we will not know who the individual visitors are. We may use cookies to store preferences; record session information; develop information about Site visitors preferences and interests; record past activity at a website in order to provide better service when you return to our Site; or customize web page content based on information you voluntarily provide.

You can disable cookies using your Internet browser settings. Please consult your browsers help function for information on how to disable cookies. Note that if you disable cookies, certain features of our Site may not function properly.

YOUR CONSENT

Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information may be given in various ways. Consent can be express (for example, orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and disclosures of personal information) or implied (for example, when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested) or given in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your personal information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an opt out option provided, if any. Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian or a person having a power of attorney). Generally, by providing us with personal information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information for the purposes identified or described in this privacy Policy, if applicable, or otherwise at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information at any time by contacting us , subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. Note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide certain of our products or services.

Company collects, uses and discloses your personal information with your consent, except as permitted or required by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose personal information without your consent, for example to comply with a court order, to comply with local, federal or foreign regulations or a legally permitted inquiry by a government agency, or to collect a debt owed to us.

ACCOUNT INFORMATION

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose your Site password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify us and change your password.

SECURITY

We take reasonable steps to help protect your personal information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our custody or control, which may include safeguards to protect against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

THIRD PARTIES

This Privacy Policy addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. This Policy does not apply to and we are in no way responsible for the information that you disclose to others, whether they are event providers, Site visitors/users, bidders, buyers, or sellers on our Site or other sites throughout the Internet. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

ACCESS, CORRECTION AND CONTACTING US

We may establish and maintain a file of your personal information for the purposes described above. If you wish to request access or correction of your personal information in our custody or control, you may contact us at policies@naturalhairmag.com. Your right to access or correct your personal information is subject to applicable legal restrictions. If you wish to withdraw consent, make inquiries or complaints or have other concerns about our personal information practices, you may contact us at policies@naturalhairmag.com.

LINKS

This Site may contain links to other websites. Please recognize that we do not control these third party websites and this Privacy Policy will not apply to those websites. You should consult each applicable privacy policy before using another linked website.

HOW WE NOTIFY YOU OF CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the amended terms on the Site. If we change how we use your personal information, you will be notified by email and may opt-out at that time. However, if you have opted-out of all communication with the Site you will not be contacted, nor will your information be used in this new manner.
